Haunter is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Vincenzo Natali.
A teenager is stuck in a time loop that is not quite the same each time.
She must uncover the truth but her actions have
consequences for herself and others.
Lisa, played by Abigail Breslin.
The Pale Man, played by Stephen McHattie.
Olivia's Father, played by David Hewlett.
Edgar, played by David Knoll.
Bruce, played by Peter Outerbridge.
Carol, played by Michelle Nolden.
Haunter is a 2013 Canadian supernatural horror  film directed by Vincenzo
Natali, written by Brian King, and starring Abigail Breslin.
The film premiered at the 2013 South by Southwest Film
Festival, and was picked up for U.S.
distribution there by IFC Midnight.
The film explores themes of afterlife, haunted
house, possession, house, serial killer.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.